A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Politics - New York City Office, Series J.1 FA345
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Office of the Governor, 1958-1971; 5; 14 Document Box(es)
  - Magazines Featuring NAR - The Miami Herald, "Why I Run", August 4, 1968 (Box 81, Folder 887)
    Special paid political advertising supplement.
    Used in Rockefeller Archive Center Newsletter- negative attached.
- State Issues Files, 1973-1975; 6; 12 Record Cartons
  Subseries 6 is arranged alphabetically by state.
  This subseries is composed of topical records on state issues that document Rockefeller's speeches and public activities from early 1973 through 1975. His support of other Republicans, particularly during the 1974 congressional campaigns, is also shown here. These state files contain issues and political memoranda for all 50 states, the District of Columbia, Guam, and Puerto Rico. Some of the states are more fully represented than others, particularly those which Rockefeller visited. For such states, there are background binders prepared for speeches he gave on behalf of Republican congressional and state candidates. These binders include itineraries, information on the respective state political government structure, statewide issues, and local issues for specific urban areas. There are also substantial newspaper clippings detailing political themes and events in each state.
  - Alabama (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Alabama - Political (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Alabama - Issues (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Alabama - Political (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Alaska (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - Alaska - Political (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Alaska - Issues (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - Alaska - Energy, Alaska Pipeline (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Arizona (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Arizona - Political (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Arizona - Issues (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - Arizona - Phoenix, Trunk 'n Tusk Dinner, October 25, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Phoenix, Arizona, Press Conference, Phoenix Press Club, October 25, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Arizona - Tuscon, Trunk 'n Tusk Dinner, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - Tucson, Arizona, KVOA - TV Taping, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Tempe, Arizona, Arizona State University, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - Tucson, Arizona, Airport Press Conference, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Tucson, Arizona, University of Arizona, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Tucson, Arizona, Press Conference, October 26, 1973 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - Arizona (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Arkansas (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Arkansas - Issues (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - Arkansas - Political (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Arkansas - Binders (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Arkansas, September 1975 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - Arkansas - Political (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - California - Los Angeles, Town Hall Meeting, September 11, 1973 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - California - Issues (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - California (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - California - Political (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Colorado - Political (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Colorado - Issues (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Colorado (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Colorado - NAR Visit, Fossil Fuels Conference, Dinner, January 31, 1974 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Connecticut (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Connecticut - Issues (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Connecticut - Political (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Delaware (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Delaware - Issues (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Delaware - Political (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - District of Columbia (Box 83, Folder 15)
  - District of Columbia - Issues (Box 83, Folder 16)
  - District of Columbia - Political (Box 83, Folder 17)
  - Florida (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Florida - Hugh Morrow Binder (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Florida - NAR Binder (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Florida (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Florida - Issues (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Florida - Political (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Florida - Gurney (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Georgia (Box 84, Folder 8)
  - Georgia - Political (Box 84, Folder 9)
  - Georgia - Issues (Box 84, Folder 10)
  - Guam (Box 84, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii (Box 84, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii - Issues (Box 84, Folder 13)
  - Hawaii - Political (Box 84, Folder 14)
  - Idaho (Box 84, Folder 15)
  - Idaho - Political (Box 84, Folder 16)
  - Idaho - Issues (Box 84, Folder 17)
  - Illinois (Box 84, Folder 18)
  - Illinois - Political (Box 84, Folder 19)
  - Illinois - Issues (Box 84, Folder 20)
  - Illinois - Extra Copies of Briefing Books (Box 84, Folder 21)
  - Illinois - NAR Visit, Clippings, February 9, 1974 (Box 84, Folder 22)
  - Illinois - Cities (Box 84, Folder 23)
  - Illinois - Anderson, post-February 9, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - Illinois - Hugh Morrow (Box 85, Folder 2)
  - Illinois - Anderson, pre-February 9, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 3)
  - Illinois - Watergate, Impeachment (Box 85, Folder 4)
  - Illinois - Chicago - Executives Club Luncheon, September 28, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 5)
  - Chicago, Illinois, Meeting with Students, September 28, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 6)
  - Illinois - Political (Box 85, Folder 7)
  - Illinois - Political, October 1975 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Illinois - Issues, October 1975 (Box 85, Folder 9)
  - Indiana (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Indiana - Issues (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Indiana - Political (Box 85, Folder 12)
  - Iowa (Box 85, Folder 13)
  - Des Moines, Iowa, Press Conference, October 30, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 14)
  - Iowa - Des Moines, Iowa Republican State Committee Dinner, October 30, 1973 (Box 85, Folder 15)
  - Iowa - Issues (Box 85, Folder 16)
  - Iowa - Political (Box 85, Folder 17)
  - Iowa (Box 85, Folder 18)
  - Kansas (Box 85, Folder 19)
  - Kansas - Political (Box 85, Folder 20)
  - Kansas - Issues (Box 85, Folder 21)
  - Kansas - NAR Kansas Trip, February 13, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Kansas (Box 85, Folder 23)
  - Kentucky (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Kentucky - Energy (Box 86, Folder 2)
  - Kentucky - Issues (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - Kentucky - Political (Box 86, Folder 4)
  - Louisiana (Box 86, Folder 5)
  - Louisiana - New Orleans, American Political Science Association, September 5, 1973 (Box 86, Folder 6)
  - Louisiana - Issues (Box 86, Folder 7)
  - Louisiana - Political (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - Maine (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - Maine - Hugh Morrow Folder (Box 86, Folder 10)
  - Maine - Energy (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Maine (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Maine - Political (Box 86, Folder 13)
  - Maine - Issues (Box 86, Folder 14)
  - Maine - Issues (Not Used) (Box 86, Folder 15)
  - Maine (Box 86, Folder 16)
  - Maine - Politics, 1975 (Box 86, Folder 17)
  - Maryland (Box 86, Folder 18)
  - Maryland - Political (Box 86, Folder 19)
  - Maryland - Issues (Box 86, Folder 20)
  - Massachusetts (Box 87, Folder 1)
  - Massachusetts (Box 87, Folder 2)
  - Massachusetts - Political (Box 87, Folder 3)
  - Massachusetts - Issues (Box 87, Folder 4)
  - Massachusetts - Busing Crisis (Box 87, Folder 5)
  - Massachusetts - NAR Visit, Boston, March 13, 1974 (Box 87, Folder 6)
  - Massachusetts - Sargent, pre-NAR Visit (Box 87, Folder 7)
  - Massachusetts - Sargent, post-NAR Visit (Box 87, Folder 8)
  - Massachusetts (Box 87, Folder 9)
  - Massachusetts - Hugh Morrow Folder (Box 87, Folder 10)
  - Michigan (Box 87, Folder 11)
  - Michigan - Ralph Nader Congress Project (Box 87, Folder 12)
  - Michigan - James Hoffa (Box 87, Folder 13)
  - Michigan - Binders (Box 87, Folder 14)
  - Michigan - Special Congressional District Elections (Box 87, Folder 15)
  - Michigan - Issues (Box 87, Folder 16)
  - Michigan - Detroit (Box 87, Folder 17)
  - Michigan - Mt. Clemens, Michigan Macomb County Republican Dinner, September 29, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 18)
  - Michigan (Box 87, Folder 19)
  - Michigan - Political (Box 87, Folder 20)
  - Michigan - Issues (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Minnesota (Box 88, Folder 2)
  - Minnesota - Political (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Minnesota - Issues (Box 88, Folder 4)
  - Mississippi (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Mississippi - Issues (Box 88, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi - Political (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Missouri (Box 88, Folder 8)
  - Missouri - Binders (Box 88, Folder 9)
  - Missouri - Issues (Box 88, Folder 10)
  - Missouri - Political (Box 88, Folder 11)
  - Kansas City, Missouri Speech (Box 88, Folder 12)
  - Montana (Box 88, Folder 13)
  - Montana - Issues (Box 88, Folder 14)
  - Montana (Box 88, Folder 15)
  - Montana - Political (Box 88, Folder 16)
  - Nebraska (Box 88, Folder 17)
  - Nebraska - Political (Box 88, Folder 18)
  - Nebraska - Issues (Box 88, Folder 19)
  - Nebraska - NAR Visit, Founders' Day Luncheon, April 6, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 20)
  - Nebraska - Hruska - post-April 6, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 21)
  - Nebraska - Hruska - pre-April 6, 1974 (Box 88, Folder 22)
  - Nebraska - Binders (Box 88, Folder 23)
  - Nevada (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Nevada - Political (Box 89, Folder 2)
  - Nevada - Issues (Box 89, Folder 3)
  - New Hampshire (Box 89, Folder 4)
  - New Hampshire - Issues (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - New Hampshire - Political (Box 89, Folder 6)
  - New Hampshire - Political, Wyman-Durkin United States Senate Race, 1974-1975 (Box 89, Folder 7)
  - New Jersey (Box 89, Folder 8)
  - New Jersey - NAR Gift to Ronan and All Related Clippings (Box 89, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey - Binder (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - New Jersey - Issues, Current (Box 89, Folder 11)
  - New Jersey - Issues, Material for NAR Trip, January 1975 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - New Jersey - Issues - Old (Box 89, Folder 13)
  - New Jersey - Issues (Box 89, Folder 14)
  - New Jersey - Political (Box 89, Folder 15)
  - New Mexico (Box 89, Folder 16)
  - New Mexico - Political (Box 89, Folder 17)
  - New Mexico - Issues (Box 89, Folder 18)
  - New Mexico - Political and Issues (Box 89, Folder 19)
  - New York (Box 89, Folder 20)
  - New York State - Issues (Box 89, Folder 21)
  - North Carolina (Box 89, Folder 22)
  - North Carolina - Political (Box 89, Folder 23)
  - North Carolina - Issues (Box 89, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina - Political and Issues (Box 89, Folder 25)
  - North Dakota (Box 89, Folder 26)
  - North Dakota - Binders (Box 89, Folder 27)
  - North Dakota - Political (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - Minot, North Dakota, Press Conference, November 26, 1973 (Box 90, Folder 2)
  - Ohio - Binders (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Ohio (Box 90, Folder 4)
  - Ohio - Impeachment (Box 90, Folder 5)
  - Ohio - Political (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Ohio - Issues (Box 90, Folder 7)
  - Okalahoma, September 13, 1975 (Box 90, Folder 8)
  - Okalahoma - Political (Box 90, Folder 9)
  - Okalahoma - Issues (Box 90, Folder 10)
  - Okalahoma - Agriculture (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Okalahoma - Oil, Energy (Box 90, Folder 12)
  - Okalahoma - Arrangements (Box 90, Folder 13)
  - Okalahoma - Political (Box 90, Folder 14)
  - Oregon - Politics (Box 90, Folder 15)
  - Oregon (Box 90, Folder 16)
  - Oregon (Box 90, Folder 17)
  - Oregon - Political, Governor McCall (Box 90, Folder 18)
  - Oregon - Dorchester Conference (Box 90, Folder 19)
  - Oregon - Issues Clippings (Box 90, Folder 20)
  - Oregon - Political Clippings (Box 90, Folder 21)
  - Oregon - Political (Box 90, Folder 22)
  - Pennsylvania (Box 91, Folder 1)
  - Pennsylvania - Binders (Box 91, Folder 2)
  - Pennsylvania - Political (Box 91, Folder 3)
  - Pennsylvania - Political (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Puerto Rico (Box 91, Folder 5)
  - Puerto Rico - Issues (Box 91, Folder 6)
  - Puerto Rico - Political (Box 91, Folder 7)
  - Rhode Island (Box 91, Folder 8)
  - Rhode Island - Political (Box 91, Folder 9)
  - Rhode Island - Issues (Box 91, Folder 10)
  - Rhode Island - Binders (Box 91, Folder 11)
  - South Dakota - Issues (Box 91, Folder 12)
  - South Dakota - Political (Box 91, Folder 13)
  - South Dakota (Box 91, Folder 14)
  - South Dakota - Binders (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - South Carolina (Box 91, Folder 16)
  - South Carolina - Political, August 1975 (Box 91, Folder 17)
  - South Dakota (Box 91, Folder 18)
  - Tennessee (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Tennessee - Political (Box 92, Folder 2)
  - Tennessee - Issues (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Texas (Box 92, Folder 4)
  - Texas - Issues (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Texas - Political (Box 92, Folder 6)
  - Texas - Political (Box 92, Folder 7)
  - Texas - NAR Clippings, September 1975 (Box 92, Folder 8)
  - Texas - Issues, September 1975 (Box 92, Folder 9)
  - Texas - Politics, September 1975 (Box 92, Folder 10)
  - Texas, September 1975 (Box 92, Folder 11)
  - Texas - NAR Visit, Dallas Council of World Affairs, February 21, 1974 (Box 92, Folder 12)
  - Utah (Box 92, Folder 13)
  - Utah - Political (Box 92, Folder 14)
  - Utah - Gifts (Box 92, Folder 15)
  - Utah - Issues (Box 92, Folder 16)
  - Vermont (Box 92, Folder 17)
  - Vermont - Political (Box 92, Folder 18)
  - Vermont - Issues (Box 92, Folder 19)
  - Virgin Islands (Box 92, Folder 20)
  - Virginia (Box 92, Folder 21)
  - Virginia - Issues (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - Virginia - Political (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - Virginia - Political, 1975 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - Washington (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - Washington - Issues (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - Washington - Binders (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - Washington - Political (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - West Virginia (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - West Virginia - Political (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - West Virginia - Issues (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - West Virginia (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Wisconsin (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - Wisconsin - Issues (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - Wisconsin - Political and Issues (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - Wisconsin - Politics, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - Wisconsin - Issues, 1975 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Wyoming (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - Wyoming - Issues (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - Wyoming - Political (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - Wyoming - Binder (Box 93, Folder 17)